Stu Coston

Digital Designer.



Profile

For the last 6 years I've worked as a project manager on \$2.3B worth of Government programs and a number of large scale construction projects. During this time, I fell in love with graphic and website design and development. I have been designing and developing digital experiences on the side for brands, businesses, and start-ups for about 5 years but I'm ready to take it full-time. A creative front-end developer at heart, my passion is constructing elegant, engaging, and easy-to-use websites through well-crafted code or popular CMSs.

Skills



Work History

Program and Contracts Manager 2012-2017
United States Air Force

Front-End Developer and Copywriter 2014-2017
Freelance

Founder - Digital Agency 2017-2019
Goby Creative

Assistant Project Manager
2018-Present
CDI Contractors

Education

United States Air Force Academy 2008-2012
Bachelor of Science
Systems Engineering

Experience

Leadership

Managed 25 person department overseeing \$800M+ of Government assets

Led 9 person cross-functional team to on-time award of \$450M production contract

Led \$17.5M test project with a 40 person team; developed a test operations schedule that challenged the status quo and saved \$700K and 3 weeks to the project

Led 3-person team for procurement of an \$80M Information Technology services contract

Initiative

Learned html, css, and js during my free time from work because I wanted to host an online magazine for my family's vacations

Launched a digital marketing agency and quickly realized I'm a designer, not a salesman

Organized 72-person department into teams of 3-5 and delegated 300+ task schedule for efficient contract transition

Communication

Prepared a 4 year forecast for a \$1.3B pilot training system -- built relationships with vendors and end users to understand funding requirements and presented requirements to leadership to secure funding

Established communication and organizational standards across company for Asana, Slack, shared drives, and Microsoft Teams in order to maximize communication efficiency

Created cross-functional team to identify and write 50+ pages of requirements to scope \$450M procurement contract